You got famous
off the hype, too.
The dream guy, huh?
Music alone
wouldn't make you famous!
You want clout?
You want clout, huh?
I'll give you that.
Henry,
see if we can re-edit
what we've got,
so Phil and January
aren't so obviously
being paired up.
If Phil quits,
we're screwed.
And please
draft a PR statement ASAP.
Candy,
check our talent list.
Reach out to everyone
on our shortlist.
Contact them.
Cole,
I'm sorry.
Do you own this place?
Why are you still here?
Candy's.
The first time
I worked late,
I was so busy
I forgot to eat.
I ended up
in the hospital.
Back then,
I worked my ass off.
But nothing I did
was good enough.
It took me three years
to finally get it right.
I think
it'll take me six years.
No way.
You've been here
less than a month
and you're already
doing great.
Really?
Yeah.
You're so busy
and you still noticed me?
That means a lot.
Eat up.
Then go home.
But the statement...
I'm not done yet.
Work never ends.
If you want,
I'll come up with
more ideas tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am.
What?
You eat like...
a little puppy.
I've always been
afraid of love
until
someone came along
with a key
and unlocked my heart.
They saw
every secret
I'd been hiding.
That's when I realized
I loved so fiercely
because I wanted
to be loved.